Spock War Posters Collection
Spock War Posters Collection
- World War II
  - "This World Cannot Exist Half Slave & Half Free", 1942; SPOCK-WWII-8; 25cm / 18cm black, white and sepia tones (Map-case 57)
    Type: Freedom
    Description: Family cowering against a wall
  - My Daddy Bought Me A Government Bond of the 3d Liberty Loan – Did Yours?, 1932; SPOCK-WWII-9; 76cm / 51cm multi (Map-case 57)
    Description: Small girl holding a bond
    Printer: U.S. Printing & Lithograph Co., New York
  - Buy Liberty Bonds – Give Them for 2 ½ Million Starving Armenians, Syrians, Greeks..., SPOCK-WWII-10; 30cm / 45cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 57)
    Description: For Armenian & Syrian Relief
  - Mayor's Committee for Mobilization of New York at War I NEED AMERICA NEEDS ME ne 13th, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-11; 56cm / 36cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 57)
    Type: Mobilization of New York at War
    Description: A hand holding a sword
  - Don't Let Him Down!, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-12; 102cm / 76cm red, white, black and red (Map-case 57)
    Type: Production
    Description: Soldier in a tank
    Printer: GPO. Division of Information, Office for Emergency Management, Washington, D.C.
  - He's a "Fighting Fool" – Give Him the Best You've Got! More Production!, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-13; 102cm / 72cm black, white and sepia (Map-case 57)
    Description: Soldier carrying a gun
    Printer: GPO, War Production Board, Washington, D.C.
  - Kindly Give It Your Personal Attention, Will You? More Production, SPOCK-WWII-14; 102cm / 72cm black, white, and green (Map-case 57)
    Description: Soldier in battle
    Printer: GPO, War Production Board
  - "Every man, woman & child is a partner" President Roosevelt In 1942 60,000 planes, 45,000 tanks, 20,000 AA Guns, 8,000,000 tons of ships, SPOCK-WWII-15; 71cm / 102cm red, white, and blue and black and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of American people
  - America's Answer! PRODUCTION, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-16; 76cm / 102cm multi (Map-case 57)
    Description: Hand holding a wrench
    Printer: GPO, Division of Information
  - Men Working TOGETHER!, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-17; 76cm / 102cm black, white, and yellow (Map-case 57)
    Description: Soldier, sailor, & worker standing together
    Printer: GPO, Office for Emergency Management, Washington, D.C.
  - Tighten Your Grip!, SPOCK-WWII-18; 54cm / 31cm multi (Map-case 57)
    Description: Wrench destroying the Nazi symbol
    Printer: Printed for H.M. Stationary Office by Fosh & Cross Ltd. London
  - Give 'Em Both Barrels, 1941; SPOCK-WWII-19; 102cm / 72cm multi (Map-case 57)
    Description: Soldier with a machine gun & a worker with a bolt gun
    Printer: GPO, Division of Information, Office For Emergency Management
  - Your Scrap... brought it down – Keep scrapping – Rubber, Metal, Rags..., 1942; SPOCK-WWII-20; 102cm / 72cm red, white, yellow, and black (Map-case 57)
    Type: Scrapping
    Description: Nazi plane going down in flames
    Printer: GPO, War Production Board, Bureau of Industrial Conservation
  - Wanted For Victory – Waste Paper, Old Rags, Scrap Metals Old Rubber – Get In The Scrap Sell To a Collector Give to a Charity, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-21; 69cm / 52cm black, white and red (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of a family collecting scraps
  - Keep Scrapping – America needs more Rubber, Metals, Rags, Paper, Burlap, SPOCK-WWII-22; 71cm / 51cm red, white, and black (Map-case 57)
  - Get In the Scrap – America's War Industries Need Metals, Paper, Old Rags, & Rubber..., SPOCK-WWII-23; 72cm / 51cm red, white, and black (Map-case 57)
  - This Man Is Your Friend... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-24; 51cm / 39cm blue and white (Map-case 57)
    Type: This Man Is Your Friend...
    Description: Black & white photo of soldier - Australian
  - This Man Is Your Friend... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-25; 51cm / 39cm blue and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of soldier - Russian
  - This Man Is Your Friend... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-26; 51cm / 39cm blue and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of soldier - Canadian
  - This Man Is Your Friend... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-27; 3 copies 51cm / 39cm blue and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of soldier - Englishman
  - This Man Is Your Friend... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-28; 51cm / 39cm blue and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of soldier - Ethiopian
  - This Man Is Your Friend... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-29; 51cm / 39cm blue and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of soldier – Dutch Sailor
  - This Man Is Your Friend... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-30; 51cm / 39cm blue and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of soldier - Chinese
  - This Man Is Your FRIEND... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-31; 102cm / 72cm blue, black, and white (Map-case 57)
    Type: This Man is Your Friend
    Description: Black & white photo of an Englishman
  - This Man Is Your FRIEND... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-32; 102cm / 72cm blue, black, and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of an Australian
  - This Man Is Your FRIEND... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-33; 102cm / 72cm blue, black, and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of an Ethiopian
  - This Man Is Your FRIEND... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-34; 102cm / 72cm blue, black, and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of Chinese
  - This Man Is Your FRIEND... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-35; 102cm / 72cm blue, black, and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of a Dutch Sailor
  - This Man Is Your FRIEND... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-36; 102cm / 72cm blue, black, and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of a Canadian
  - This Man Is Your FRIEND... He Fights For FREEDOM, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-37; 102cm / 72cm blue, black, and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: Black & white photo of a Russian
  - Save Rubber... Swap Rides, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-38; 102cm / 72cm red, white, and black (Map-case 57)
    Type: Transportation
    Printer: GPO, Office of Transportation, Washington, D.C.
  - Defend Your Country – Enlist Now in the U.S. Army, 1940; SPOCK-WWII-39; 96cm / 64cm multi (Map-case 57)
    Description: Uncle Sam in shirtsleeves with an American Eagle
    Printer: Spurgeon Tucker, New York
  - Buy US Bonds & Stamps - Keep It Up!, SPOCK-WWII-40; 3 copies 28cm / 53cm yellow, black, white, and red (Map-case 57)
    Type: U.S. Bonds & Stamps
    Description: Military plane flying through the sky
  - America First... National Americanization Committee or US Bureau of Education, SPOCK-WWII-41; 80cm / 50cm multi (Map-case 57)
    Type: U.S. Bureau of Education
    Description: Uncle Sam welcoming foreigners
    Printer: Allied Printing, New York City
  - Chasing the Rainbow... With the US Marines 113 Church Street New Haven, Conn., SPOCK-WWII-42; 28cm / 48cm black and white (Map-case 57)
    Description: US Marines
  - First in France – US Marines, SPOCK-WWII-43; 71cm / 53cm multi (Map-case 57)
    Description: Marines running with guns & flags
  - US Navy Requires Firemen – 2nd & 3rd Class..., SPOCK-WWII-44; 2 copies 56cm / 35cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 57)
    Printer: Van Dyck & Co., Inc., New Haven, Connecticut
  - Speed Means Safety for Our Ships The US Navy's Need 7,000 Firemen Now! Be A Speedmaker, SPOCK-WWII-45; 106cm / 71cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 57)
  - Navy Strikes Now – Follow the Flag for Freedom Your Choice – Naval Reserve, Coast Guard, or Navy, SPOCK-WWII-46; 2 copies 57cm / 35cm multi (Map-case 57)
    Description: Liberty leading men & ships into battle
    Printer: Navy Recruiting Bureau, NY
  - Shall Uncle Sam's Navy Suffer Our Soldiers Going "Over There" On Our Transports to Sink? For Lack of Firemen, 7,000 Needed Now!, SPOCK-WWII-47; 107cm / 72cm red, white and blue (Map-case 57)
  - You, Wireless Fans, Help the Navy Get the Hun Submarine 1000 Radio Men Wanted In the Navy & the Naval Reserve, SPOCK-WWII-48; 113cm / 72cm multi (Map-case 57)
    Description: Man with a headset
    Printer: US Navy Recruiting Bureau
  - Life In The Navy – Food For Fighters.. .Come In For Fighting & Big Eats & ENLIST IN THE NAVY, SPOCK-WWII-49; 36cm / 43cm black, white, and red (Map-case 57)
    Description: Various black & white photos of Navy rations & sailors
    Printer: U.S. Navy Recruiting Bureau, New York
  - We Are Now In This War - We Are In It All The Way.. .President Roosevelt, Address to the Nation, December 9, 1941", SPOCK-WWII-50; 61cm / 45cm red, white, blue, and black (Map-case 57)
    Type: War, announcement
    Printer: U.S. Government Printing Office
  - Buy War Bonds, Stamps for Victory, SPOCK-WWII-51; 4 copies 70cm / 57cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 57)
    Description: Poster in the shape of Uncle Sam's hat
    Printer: Display Committee, Treasury Department
  - "You buy 'em we'll fly 'em!" War Bond Stamps The More Bonds You Buy – The More Planes Will Fly, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-52; 2 copies 71cm / 51cm multi (Map-case 57)
    Type: War Bond Stamps
    Description: Pilot flying in a plane – other planes flying in the background
  - US Treasury News Bulletin... For Victory Buy U.S. War Bonds & Stamps, SPOCK-WWII-53; 31cm / 48cm black and white (Map-case 57)
    Type: War Bonds & Stamps
    Description: Black & white photo of a mural of war
  - Women – Your Country Needs You... Woman's Committee, Council of National Defense, SPOCK-WWII-54; 72cm / 53cm red, white and black (Map-case 57)
    Type: Women & War
  - Women In The War – We Can't Win Without Them, 1942; SPOCK-WWII-55; 102cm / 72cm red, white, blue, and black (Map-case 57)
    Description: Photo of a woman working with a machine
    Printer: GPO, War Manpower Commission, Washington, D.C.
- Miscellaneous World War I and II
  - Window decal, "Buy Bonds Third Liberty Loan", 14.5cm / 14.5cm red, white, blue (Map-case 56)
  - Postcard, soldier running with gun "On les aura! Souscrivez aux Bons de la Defense Nationale", 13.5cm / 9cm (Map-case 56)
  - Door hanger, in shape of a bell, "Ring Me Again, Third Liberty Loan, Buy U.S. Government Bonds", 28cm / 20cm red, white, blue (Map-case 56)
  - Flyer, soldier and sailor with books, "We Want Books - Victory Book Campaign Sponsored by American Library Association, American Red Cross, United Service Organization for National Defense, Inc.", 29cm / 18.5cm green, salmon, cream, white (Map-case 56)
  - Flyer, "Enlist with the Marines, Information at Marine Corps Recruiting Station: 19 Congress Ave., New Haven, Conn.", 21cm / 16.5cm red, white (Map-case 56)
  - Calendar, in French, showing soldier with French flag and sword, fighting an eagle, "4e Emprunt de la Defense Nationale, Credit Lyonnais", 2 copies 24cm / 31cm multi (Map-case 56)
  - Advertisements, many pages stapled together, "Victory Loan Volunteer Advertising Copy," from Liberty Loan Committee, Chicago, 59cm / 45cm black and white (Map-case 56)
- Unidentified world wars
  - Britishers You're Needed, SPOCK #1; 105cm / 71cm multi (Map-case 58)
    Type: Britishers
    Description: Man crossing the Atlantic
    Printer: Albert Frank & Co. NY Agents
  - Britishers – Enlist Today!, SPOCK #2; 104cm / 68cm multi (Map-case 58)
    Description: British flag
  - Uphold the Flag, SPOCK #3; 104cm / 70cm multi (Map-case 58)
    Type: Canadian
    Description: Flag & donation boxes
    Printer: Howell Lith. Ltd Hamilton
  - Navy Wants Men – The Royal Naval Canadian Volunteer Reserve..., SPOCK #4; 107cm / 72cm multi – mostly blue and white (Map-case 58)
    Type: Canadian Navy
    Description: Sailors in a crow's nest
    Printer: Mortimer Co., Ltd – Ottowa, Montreal, Toronto
  - Is Your Name on the Honor Roll - 4th Liberty Loan, SPOCK #5; 64cm / 43cm maroon, teal, and white (Map-case 58)
    Type: Fourth Liberty Loan
  - Honor Roll... Fourth Liberty Loan, SPOCK #6; 2 copies 69cm / 50cm red, white and blue (Map-case 58)
    Description: Flag Flying
    Printer: Edward & Deutsch Litho. Co. Chicago
  - GIVE!, SPOCK #7; 5 copies 34cm / 68 cm blue and white (Map-case 58)
    Type: Give
  - We Clear The Way For Your Fighting Dollars – Buy 4th Liberty Loan US Government Bonds, SPOCK #8; 71cm / 53cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 58)
    Description: Navy sailor with a gun
  - LEND!, SPOCK #9; 51cm / 72cm red and white (Map-case 58)
    Type: Lend
    Printer: Carey Print Lith. NY
  - Buy to-day at any bank – buy liberty bonds, SPOCK #10; 72cm / 57cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 58)
    Description: Bullseye
  - His Liberty Bond – Paid For In Full..., SPOCK #11; 58cm / 41cm black, white, and red (Map-case 58)
    Description: Dead soldier on the battlefield
  - Help our town win the right to fly this Flag 3d Liberty Loan Is Your Name on the Honor Roll?, SPOCK #12; 67cm / 98cm red, white, blue, and black (Map-case 58)
    Type: Third Liberty Loan
    Printer: Capital Publishing, Inc., Washington, D.C.
  - Third Liberty Loan Subscriber, SPOCK #13; 23cm / 18cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 58)
    Description: Flag / Liberty Bell – box where "name of owner of 3d Liberty Loan Bond to be written here"
  - Premiers au Feu Means in French First To Fight in English US Marines Enlist Today at 19 Congress Ave., New Haven, CT, SPOCK #14; 107cm / 72cm green, white, orange, and gray (Map-case 58)
    Description: Smiling Marine face
  - Enlist with Marines – Information at Marine Corps Recruiting Station, SPOCK #15; 21cm / 26cm red and white (Map-case 58)
  - E-E-E-Yah-Yip Go Over With US Marines, SPOCK #16; 2 copies 71cm / 54cm Orange, black, and white (Map-case 58)
    Description: Soldier with a bayonet
  - Enlist In the Navy – To Arms – US Navy Recruiting Station, SPOCK #17; 105cm / 70cm black, white, yellow and red (Map-case 58)
    Description: Sailor blowing a bugle
  - Be Ready! A U.S. Navy Recruiting Party will visit... See them on these dates..., SPOCK #18; 30cm / 48cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 58)
    Description: Sailor with a bayonet standing in from of an American flag
  - USN – This Gun Is "Over There", Where Are You? Man the Guns of the Navy, Get In the Game! Enlist, SPOCK #19; 56cm / 35cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 58)
    Description: Machine gun
  - Warding Off A Night Attack... Navy Recruiting Station, SPOCK #20; 43cm / 35cm red, white, and black (Map-case 58)
    Description: Black & white photo of a battleship at night
  - These Men Have COME ACROSS, They Are at the Front NOW, JOIN THEM, ENLIST in the Navy, SPOCK #21; 28cm / 53cm multi (Map-case 58)
    Description: Four men loading a missile into a launcher
  - Invest, SPOCK #22; 77cm / 51cm red, white and blue (Map-case 58)
    Type: Victory Bonds
    Description: Large blue V
    Printer: Strobridge Litho. Co., Cincinnati
  - Buy Another – Join the YD – Victory Liberty Loan, SPOCK #23; 64cm / 51cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 58)
  - Show Your Button – Victory Liberty Loan, SPOCK #24; 10cm / 51cm blue and white (Map-case 58)
  - Finish The Job, Subscribe To The "Victory" Liberty Loan, SPOCK #25; 2 copies 81cm / 56cm yellow, blue, and green (Map-case 58)
    Description: Large blue "V" surrounded by a laurel crown
  - Show Your Button – Victory Liberty Loan, SPOCK #26; 69cm / 51cm blue and white (Map-case 58)
  - War Exhibit Train – Trophies from the Fighting Front Death Dealing Machines of War, From Land-Sea-Air! Victory Liberty Loan, SPOCK #27; 107cm / 71cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 58)
    Printer: Walton & Spencer, Co.
  - Bring Him Home With the Victory Loan, SPOCK #28; 90cm / 61cm multi (Map-case 58)
    Description: Soldier sitting with gun & belongings
  - Honor Roll... Victory Liberty Loan, SPOCK #29; 52cm / 51cm red, white and blue (Map-case 58)
    Description: V flag flying
    Printer: Regensteiner Colortype Co., Chicago
  - Buy Another, Join the YD – Victory Liberty Loan, SPOCK #30; 64cm / 50cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 58)
  - Think – Have You Bought Your Limit? Fourth Liberty Loan, SPOCK #31; 16cm / 102cm red, white, and blue (Map-case 58)
  - "Would Nathan Hale Hold Back If He Were Here Today?".. Buy thrift stamps & war saving certificates, SPOCK #32; 71cm / 53cm Brown and white (Map-case 58)
    Type: War Saving Certificates
    Description: Statue of Nathan Hale
    Printer: Columbia/Hartford
- Vietnam
  - Dr. Spock Is Worried..., undated; Vietnam #1; 61cm/ 41 cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Dr. Spock standing with a small girl, SANE advertisement first published in the New York Times
    Artist: n/a
    Condition: no damage (in a plastic cover)
  - Son Chan Valley, Vietnam "I'm Sorry Sir, but my men refuse to go... We cannot move out" Lieutenant in Command of Company A — The End", undated; Vietnam #2; 45cm / 58cm Black and tan (Map-case 59)
    Description: Photo of soldiers, smiling, making peace signs
    Artist: SU Negrin
    Condition: no damage
  - Vietnamization Turns Children into Soldiers, Clergy and Laymen concerned..., undated; Vietnam #3; 57cm / 43 cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Photo of young boy soldiers
    Artist: Philip Jones Griffiths-Magnum
    Printer: nia
  - The Vietnam War Continues — September 1969: / 44,798 American Soldiers Are Dead / 93,738 Saigon Government Soldiers Are Dead / 546,804 N.L.F.& North Vietnamese Soldiers Are Dead / The October Draft Call is 29,000 — Pray For Peace, Sep 1969; Vietnam #4; 58cm / 43cm Red, green, white (Map-case 59)
    Artist: Statistics from the Department of Defense
  - The Vietnam War Continues — November 1969: / 46, 112 American Soldiers Are Dead / 96, 456 Saigon Government Soldiers Are Dead / 566,501 N.L.F. & North Vietnamese Soldiers Are Dead The December Draft Call is 9,000 — Pray For Peace, Nov 1969; Vietnam #5; 58cm / 43cm Black, maroon, white (Map-case 59)
  - The Vietnam War Continues — December 1969: / 46, 682 American Soldiers Are Dead / 98, 016 Saigon Government Soldiers Are Dead / 577,445 N.L.F. & North Vietnamese Soldiers Are Dead / The January Draft Call is 12,500 — Pray For Peace, Dec 1969; Vietnam #6; 58cm / 43cm Black, green, white (Map-case 59)
  - The Vietnam War Continues — January 1970: / 47,159 American Soldiers Are Dead / 99,454 Saigon Government Soldiers Are Dead / 586,543 N.L.F. & North Vietnamese Soldiers Are Dead The February Draft Call is 19,000 — Pray For Peace, Jan 1970; Vietnam #7; 58cm / 43cm Red, blue, white (Map-case 59)
  - The Vietnam War Continues — April 1970: / 49,024 American Soldiers Are Dead / 104,485 Saigon Government Soldiers Are Dead / 618.061 N.L.F. & North Vietnamese Soldiers Are Dead / The May Draft Call is 15,000 — Pray For Peace, Apr 1970; Vietnam #8; 58cm / 43cm(two copies) Black, red, white (Map-case 59)
  - The Vietnam War Continues — December 1970: / 52, 969 American Soldiers Are Dead / 117,980 Saigon Government Soldiers Are Dead / 684,948 N.L.F. & North Vietnamese Soldiers Are Dead / JANUARY DRAFT FIGURES NOT AVAILBALE AT PRINTING, Dec 1970; Vietnam #9; 58cm / 43cm Red, green, white (Map-case 59)
  - The Vietnam War Continues — January 1971: / 53,305 American Soldiers Are Dead / 119,451 Saigon Government Soldiers Are Dead / 691,881 N.L.F. & North Vietnamese Soldiers Are Dead / The January Draft Call is 17,000 — Pray For Peace, Jan 1971; Vietnam #10; 58cm / 43cm Red, brown, white (Map-case 59)
  - How Many More Must Die? March Against Death — A Vietnam Memorial Washington, D.C. November 13-15, 1969..., undated; Vietnam #11; 57cm / 43cm Black and sepia tones (Map-case 59)
    Description: photo of small Asian children
    Artist: The New Mobilization Committee to End War In Vietnam
  - International Student Strike April 26, 1968 / Bring Troops Home Now! / End Racial Oppression - Stop the Draft / Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, Vietnam #12; 61.5cm / 44cm Red, white, blue, black (Map-case 59)
    Description: Black and white photos of war
  - "JOY PEACE And they should beat their swords into plough shares and their spears into pruning hooks. Nation shall not lift up sword against nation, neither shall they learn war anymore — Isaiah II 4", 1970; Vietnam #13; 51cm / 33cm Black, blue, white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Dove with olive branch in beak
    Artist: Marcia and Bill Drescher
  - Vietnam: Who Is the principal terrorist? Who is "precipitating" what bloodbath? Two bad arguments..., undated; Vietnam #14; 57cm / 43cm (two copies) Pink, white, and black (Map-case 59)
    Description: no damage
    Printer: Clergy & Laymen Concerned about Vietnam
    Condition:
  - WAR IS OVER! If You Want It. Love and Peace from John & Yoko, undated; Vietnam #15; 74cm / 51cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Artist: John Lennon
  - Will I have to go to war?, 1969; Vietnam #16; 73.5cm / 51cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Black and white photo of a young boy
    Artist: Conceived by Sabrina Marshall, Photo by Edith Paul Marshall
    Printer: Empathy Graphics, Inc.
  - I Can't See My Flag Anymore / I should like to be able to love my country and still love justice — Albert Camus, 1969; Vietnam #17; 74.5cm / 54cm Red, white, blue, and black (Map-case 59)
    Description: United States flag hidden by masquerade masks
    Artist: Design by Tony Palladino, Photo by Edith Marshall
    Printer: Empathy Graphics
  - GIs United against the War, Ft. Jackson - Fighting Men, undated; Vietnam #18; 55.5cm / 43cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Candid black and white photo of GIs
    Printer: GI Civil Defense Committee
  - Conscience — The Ultimate Weapon, 1968; Vietnam #19; 56cm / 42cm Black, white, and blue (Map-case 59)
    Description: Black and white photo of a woman holding a picket sign
    Artist: multi-projection/sound presentation of contemporary social issues based upon the photographs of Benedict J. Fernandez
  - Happy Holidays from the Children of Vietnam, undated; Vietnam #20; 56cm / 43cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: Black and white photo of a small Vietnamese boy
    Artist: Clergy and Laymen concerned about Vietnam
  - March On Washington — November 15 — End the War. Get Out Now! Stop The War! Stop The War Machine! Stop The Death Machine! …, undated; Vietnam #21; 63.5cm / 46cm White, blue, and green (Map-case 59)
    Description: Hand giving the peace sign
    Artist: New Mobilization Committee To End The War In Vietnam
    Printer: Amalgamated Lithographers
  - April 2nd thru 4th — Join the National Tribute to Martin Luther King, Jr., undated; Vietnam #22; 64cm / 48.5cm Black and white with some colors (Map-case 59)
    Description: Drawing of people with picket signs
    Artist: Mark Monis
    Printer: Allied Printing, Washington
    Condition: Top has some minor damage
  - They've got an invisible program to end an undeclared war backed by a silent majority... Madison Square Garden Rally: 1970 Senators for Peace and New Priorities. Thursday, March 12, 7:30 P.M., Vietnam #23; 72cm / 56cm Multi (Map-case 59)
    Description: note attached from William Meyer, Fund for New Priorities in America
    Artist: Robert Grossman
  - Vietnam For The Vietnamese — Let's Get Out Now! Stop the War Now!, undated; Vietnam #24; 72cm / 57cm Black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: "QUEEN'S COLLEGE" written on the back
    Printer: Offset Printing
    Condition: Many folds
  - Honor King End Racism, 8 Apr 1968; Vietnam #25; 55cm / 36cm black and white (Map-case 59)
    Description: note on back: Memphis March, April 8 1968 for Sanitation Workers after Dr. King assassination
    Condition: many folds
  - 1969-1970 Denison Lecture Series presents: Dr. Benjamin Spock on Nov. 9..., undated; Vietnam #26; 56cm / 36cm 2 copies copy one: Green, blue and white; copy two: Green, blue and black (Map-case 59)
    Description: Arms holding up the world